Callum Gill

callumgill99@outlook.com | Mobile: 07729387663 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/callum-gill-6a3b17179/

Portfilio website: https://musing-poincare-55331e.netlify.app

User Profile

I am a 3rd year full time student at Edge Hill university currently studying web design and development. I will have hopefully graduated from studies in July 2021. During my time at on this course I have been exposed to a range of skills from lots of fields in the web industry. Front end development (HTML, CSS, JS). Backend development (Laravel,MySQL). Also testing/UX design. From work experience I have developed many life skills this being teamwork, communication and being able to work under stressful conditions.

Education

2018 - 2021 Edge Hill University

BSc (Hons) Web Design and Development- predicted 2:1

Average results so far 68%

- One module was a creation of a website in HTML, CSS and JS which in showed me techniques and practices used in the creation of website.
- Another module was based around UX which helped me grasp the idea of the need of user interaction during the product creation to be able to add towards user satisfaction - User Design Experience
- In a module had soft knowledge of full stack deployment which will help in the process of knowledge in what over people will need to do with my work so I can have better understanding if issues arise -Server & Client-Side Scripting
- Another module showed non-user testing this helps with testing without user and how to complete this.- Web Application Development
- The final project will be a creation of a app which will need HTML, CSS and JS and UX/Design which encompasses most skills needed for front end development and help gain valuable skills. This will also be the same for my portfolio modules without the UX elements

2015 - 2017 Burnley College, Burnley

BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma in Software Development

D*D*D

2010-2015 Shuttleworth College

GCSE 9 (4B,5C) including English and Maths

Work Experience

September 2016 - September 2017 McDonalds Burnham Gate, Burnley

Responsibility's

- Being able to work in a busy environment
- Being able to work as part as team to make sure everything runs smoothly
- Checking food stock and then refilling stations so people don't run out of stock which would slow down the whole operation
- Cleaning the work stations throughout the day

September 2015 - April 2016 Fat giraffe, Padiham

Pot wash/Waiter

Responsibility's

- Cleaning the kitchen throughout the day
- Preparing food
- Washing cooking utensils / polishing cutlery
- Taking food to the customers
- Making sure everything with the food is ok after taking food out

Interests and Activities

Enjoy creating websites and sharing content for others to see. I also enjoy all kinds of sports I have played for a football team for 6 years while at university highly attending sports events for football and cricket this was not competitive and more aimed for fun but again have to be used to new people and best devise how to use certain people at their strengths.